What are you doing here?
Shiya.
I regret it.
I don't agree to you marrying Pei Ning.
We are already divorced.
It's none of your business.
Go back.
What if I say no?
Shiya.
You must come home with me right now.
Why should I?
Shiya.
I can't explain it to you clearly right now.
I don't want to lose you.
For the past three years,
I failed you.
I was always busy
and ignored your feelings.
But,
can you please not marry Pei Ning tomorrow?
What's the point of saying this now?
It's too late.
Look at you.
Why did you have to come here
just to humiliate yourself?
You don't understand.
You understand?
If you understood,
you wouldn't have agreed to divorce Shiya.
A good horse doesn't return to the old pasture.
I advise you to stop bothering Shiya.
Shiya.
I really don't know
how to explain it to you.
But you really can't marry Pei Ning tomorrow.
Did you hear what I said to you?
Are you done making a scene?
Pour me a drink.
Pei Ning
is here.
Where is Shiya?
Have you eaten?
Why did you drink so much?
Shiya hasn't been answering my calls.
Did she drink too much?
What a considerate husband.
I think you love Shiya
even more than your brother does.
Jingyan, you are drunk.
Shiya hasn't been answering my calls.
I am worried about her.
I am taking her with me.
No.
Pei Ning.
First, tell me
what method you used
in such a short time
to capture Shiya's heart.
Eddie,
she is drunk.
Take her to rest.
I'm fine.
Pei Ning.
Shiya, Pei Ning is here.
Ours was a marriage of convenience.
You didn't even show up for the divorce.
You said you were abroad and sent a lawyer.
You suddenly showed up today.
Are you afraid of gossip?
Your ex-wife suddenly became your sister-in-law,
and you're afraid of losing face.
Or do you want to say
that you want to tell me
you still love me?
If you have nothing to say, just go back.
Shiya.
Are you in there?
I'm coming in, Shiya.
Shiya.
I called you so many times,
but you didn't answer.
I was very worried about you.
Are you okay?
I just went crazy with my sisters.
I spilled wine all over myself.
I'll be out after a shower.
Then.
I'll stay with you.
You go down first.
Pei Song.
I don't know why you came here today,
but we are already over.
Please leave.
Shiya.
Shiya, please believe me.
Please leave.